<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>OCL Workshop</title>
    <link>https://oclworkshop.github.io/2019/</link>
    <description>Recent content on OCL Workshop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 16:12:19 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://oclworkshop.github.io/2019/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Call for Papers</title>
      <link>https://oclworkshop.github.io/2019/cfp.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 16:12:19 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oclworkshop.github.io/2019/cfp.html</guid>
      <description>Call For Papers Modeling started out with UML and its precursors as a graphical notation. Such visual representations enable direct intuitive capturing of reality, but they have weaknesses: for example, detailed visual representations bear the risk of becoming overcrowded faster than textual models and some of the visual features lack the level of precision required to create complete and unambiguous specifications. These weaknesses of graphical notations encouraged the development of text-based modeling languages that either integrate with or replace graphical notations for modeling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Important dates</title>
      <link>https://oclworkshop.github.io/2019/dates.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 16:51:13 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oclworkshop.github.io/2019/dates.html</guid>
      <description> Important Dates The important dates you should bear in mind for the workshop are the following:
 Submission of papers: 21 Jul 2019, AoE (extended) Notification: 25 Aug 2019, AoE Pre-Workshop CRC: 9 Sep 2019, AoE
 Post-Workshop CRC: 5 Oct 2019, AoE
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Committee</title>
      <link>https://oclworkshop.github.io/2019/committee.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 16:54:40 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oclworkshop.github.io/2019/committee.html</guid>
      <description>Organizers  Achim D. Brucker, University of Exeter, UK Gwendal Daniel, Universitat Oberta de Catalunya, Spain Frédéric Jouault, Groupe ESEO, France  Programme Committee  Thomas Baar, HTW Berlin, Germany Mira Balaban, Ben - Gurion University of the Negev, Israel Tricia Balfe, Nomos Software, Ireland Domenico Bianculli, University of Luxembourg, Luxembourg Robert Bill, Vienna University of Technology, Austria Achim D. Brucker, University of Exeter, UK Jordi Cabot, Inria - Open University of Catalonia, Spain Dan Chiorean, Babes-Bolyai University, Romania Robert Clariso, Universitat Oberta de Catalunya, Spain Tony Clark, Aston University, UK Manuel Clavel, IMDEA Software Institute, Spain Birgit Demuth, Technische Universität Dresden, Germany Martin Gogolla, University of Bremen, Germany Adolfo Sanchez-Barbudo Herrera, University of York, UK Istvan Rath, Budapest University of Technology and Economics, Hungary Jan Oliver Ringert, Tel Aviv University, Israel Bernhard Rumpe, RWTH Aachen, Germany Frédéric Tuong, Université Paris-Saclay - LRI, France Edward Willink, Willink Transformations Ltd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Program</title>
      <link>https://oclworkshop.github.io/2019/program.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 04:54:50 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oclworkshop.github.io/2019/program.html</guid>
      <description>Tentative Workshop Program  9.00-10.30: Session 1  Ed Willing: Two Decades of OCL - A Personal View Manuel Clavel and Hoàng Nguyễn Phước Bảo. Mapping OCL into SQL: Challenges and Opportunities Ahead pre-print Edward Willink. OCL Visualization - A Reality Check pre-print  10.30-11.00: Coffee Break 11.00-12.30: Session 2
 Daniel Calegari and Marcos Viera. Experimenting with functional features of the Object Constraint Language pre-print slides Robert Clarisó and Martin Gogolla.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://oclworkshop.github.io/2019/contact.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 16:55:21 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oclworkshop.github.io/2019/contact.html</guid>
      <description>How to contact You can contact us by sending an email or via twitter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Past Editions</title>
      <link>https://oclworkshop.github.io/2019/pasteditions.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oclworkshop.github.io/2019/pasteditions.html</guid>
      <description> Past Editions  OCL 2018, Copenhagen OCL 2017, Marburg OCL 2016, Saint-Malo OCL 2015, Ottawa OCL 2014, Valencia OCL 2013, Miami OCL 2012, Innsbruck OCL 2011, Zurich OCL 2010, Oslo OCL 2009, Colorado OCL 2008, Toulouse OCL 2007, Nashville OCL 2006, Genova OCL 2005, Montego Bay OCL 2004, Lisbon OCL 2003, San Francisco OCL 2001, Toronto OCL 2000, York  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News</title>
      <link>https://oclworkshop.github.io/2019/news.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 04:23:13 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oclworkshop.github.io/2019/news.html</guid>
      <description> News !!! OCL Workshop 2019 Website On-line - 2019-05-01 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>